<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MoviesApp</string>

    <string name="label">Movie Details</string>

    <string name="overview">Overview :</string>

    <string name="avengers">"As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain."</string>

    <string name="deadpool">"Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool battles the evil and powerful Cable and other bad guys to save a boy's life."</string>

    <string name="themeg">"A deep sea submersible pilot revisits his past fears in the Mariana Trench, and accidentally unleashes the seventy foot ancestor of the Great White Shark believed to be extinct."</string>

    <string name="missionimpossible">"When an IMF mission ends badly, the world is faced with dire consequences. As Ethan Hunt takes it upon himself to fulfil his original briefing, the CIA begin to question his loyalty and his motives. The IMF team find themselves in a race against time, hunted by assassins while trying to prevent a global catastrophe."</string>

    <string name="blackpanther">"King T'Challa returns home from America to the reclusive, technologically advanced African nation of Wakanda to serve as his country's new leader. However, T'Challa soon finds that he is challenged for the throne by factions within his own country as well as without. Using powers reserved to Wakandan kings, T'Challa assumes the Black Panther mantel to join with girlfriend Nakia, the queen-mother, his princess-kid sister, members of the Dora Milaje (the Wakandan 'special forces') and an American secret agent, to prevent Wakanda from being dragged into a world war."</string>

    <string name="antman">"As Scott Lang awaits expiration of his term of house detention, Hope van Dyne and Dr. Hank Pym involve him in a scheme to rescue Mrs. van Dyne from the micro-universe into which she has fallen, while two groups of schemers converge on them with intentions of stealing Dr. Pym's inventions."</string>
</resources>
